Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Full Board, 1851 -- 2020; UA003.001; 14.95 Linear Feet; 5 Volumes; 38 Digital Object(s) 38 zip files containing 670 files.; 1.83 Gigabytes
  - Secretary's files, 1855 -- 1921; UA003.001.004
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files (with index), 1900 -- 1904; UA003.001.101.00009 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 1 of 6 (with index), 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00010 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 2 of 6, 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00011 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 3 of 6, 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00012 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 4 of 6, 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00013 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 5 of 6, 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00014 (Box 101)
    - Full Board, Secretary's Files, 6 of 6, 1902 -- 1909; UA003.001.101.00015 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files, 1 of 3 (with index), 1909 -- 1917; UA003.001.101.00016 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files, 2 of 3, 1909 -- 1917; UA003.001.101.00017 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files, 3 of 3, 1909 -- 1917; UA003.001.101.00018 (Box 101)
    - Board of Trustees, Secretary's Files, 1917 -- 1921; UA003.001.101.00019 (Box 101)
  - Board of trustees files, 2000-2016; UA003.001.00001; 323 Digital Object(s); 0.85 Gigabytes
    Files bundled from several digital accessions.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2016; UA003.001.00002; 27 Digital Object(s); 29.5 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00003; 3 Digital Object(s); 1.55 Megabytes
    Closed 75 years from date of creation.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00004; 10 Digital Object(s); 13.3 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00005; 5 Digital Object(s); 9.81 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00006; 15 Digital Object(s); 29.6 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00007; 4 Digital Object(s); 5.74 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017; UA003.001.00008; 19 Digital Object(s); 21.6 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018; UA003.001.00009; 5 Digital Object(s); 10.4 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018; UA003.001.00010; 12 Digital Object(s); 18.8 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018; UA003.001.00011; 8 Digital Object(s); 31.9 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018; UA003.001.00012; 12 Digital Object(s); 27.5 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018; UA003.001.00013; 5 Digital Object(s); 2.25 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2002-11-01; UA003.001.00014; 19 Digital Object(s); 10.91 Megabytes
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2002-11-02; UA003.001.00015; 16 Digital Object(s); 8.41 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2017-11-04; UA003.001.00016; 19 Digital Object(s); 21.64 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018-05-19; UA003.001.00017; 12 Digital Object(s); 27.57 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018-11-02; UA003.001.00018; 5 Digital Object(s); 4.9 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018-11-03; UA003.001.00019; 19 Digital Object(s); 18.59 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2018-11-03; UA003.001.00020; 19 Digital Object(s); 18.62 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2019-02-07; UA003.001.00021; 2 Digital Object(s); 1.77 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2019-02-08; UA003.001.00022; 7 Digital Object(s); 5.69 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2019-02-09; UA003.001.00023; 10 Digital Object(s); 14.55 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2019-05-17; UA003.001.00024; 5 Digital Object(s); 4.84 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, 2019-05-18; UA003.001.00025; 14 Digital Object(s); 18.32 Megabytes
  - Board of Trustees files, regular session, 2019 November 01; UA003.002325; 3.6 Megabytes 4 files
  - Board of Trustees files, regular session, 2019 November 02; UA003.002326; 18.8 Megabytes 20 files
  - Board of Trustees files, special session, 2019 December 02; UA003.002327; 4 Megabytes 5 files
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 February 07; UA003.002368; 7.13 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 February 08; UA003.002369; 14.03 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 March 10; UA003.002370; 1.43 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 May 15; UA003.002371; 1.79 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 May 16; UA003.002372; 8.93 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 June 18; UA003.002373; 4.08 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 August 10; UA003.002374; 4.65 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 September 23; UA003.002375; 868.26 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 November 06; UA003.002376; 2.49 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
  - Board of Trustees files, 2020 November 07; UA003.002377; 14.17 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 12 files.
- Executive Committee, 1854 -- 2020; UA003.002; 12.55 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 46 Digital Object(s) 46 zip files containing 719 files.; 694 Megabytes
  This series contains material from Tufts University's Executive Committee from 1855 to 2000. Folders contain meeting announcements, agendas, minutes, letters, memoranda, and supplemental material (i.e., reports and current event materials). From 1855 to 1962, the work of the Executive Committee is captured in Secretary's meeting notes.
  The Executive Committee makes decisions for the entire Board when the board is not in session. Its decisions carry the weight of the full Board.
  This series is arranged chronologically by committee meeting date.
  - Working papers, 1954 -- 2000; UA003.002.001
    - Executive Committee, 1954 -- 1965; UA003.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1968; UA003.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1966 -- 1967; UA003.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1969; UA003.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1970; UA003.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, March - April, 1970; UA003.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, October - December, 1970; UA003.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, May - September, 1970; UA003.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, January 21, 1971; UA003.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, March 4, 1971; UA003.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, April 29, 1971; UA003.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, June 1, 1971; UA003.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, September 28, 1971; UA003.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1971; UA003.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, January 25-March 28, 1972; UA003.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, January 29, 1972; UA003.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, May 5, 1972; UA003.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, May 31, 1972; UA003.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, June 3, 1972; UA003.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, September 26, 1972; UA003.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
    - Executive Commitee, October 24, 1972; UA003.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
    - Executive Commitee, October 27, 1972; UA003.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - Executive Commitee, October 28, 1972; UA003.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, November 17, 1972; UA003.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, December 12, 1972; UA003.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - Executive Committee, January 23, 1973; UA003.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, January 27, 1973; UA003.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, February 27, 1973; UA003.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, March 27, 1973; UA003.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, April 24, 1973; UA003.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, May 19, 1973; UA003.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, June 2, 1973; UA003.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, September 25, 1973; UA003.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, October 23, 1973; UA003.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, November 3, 1973; UA003.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, November 27, 1973; UA003.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, January 22, 1974; UA003.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, January 26, 1974; UA003.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, February 26, 1974; UA003.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, March 26, 1974; UA003.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, April 23, 1974; UA003.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee, Trustees Meeting, Tape #1, May 5, 1972; UA003.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Executive Committee, Trustees Meeting, Tape #2, May 5, 1972; UA003.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Executive Committee, May 28, 1974; UA003.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, June 14, 1974; UA003.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, September 24, 1974; UA003.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, October 22, 1974; UA003.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, November 26, 1974; UA003.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, January 28, 1975; UA003.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, February 25, 1975; UA003.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, March 25, 1975; UA003.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, April 22, 1975; UA003.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, May 13, 1975; UA003.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, September 23, 1975; UA003.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, October 28, 1975; UA003.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, November 25, 1975; UA003.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, January 27, 1976; UA003.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Executive Committee, April 27, 1976; UA003.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, July 13, 1976; UA003.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, September 29, 1976; UA003.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, October 19, 1976; UA003.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, November 30, 1976; UA003.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, January 18, 1977; UA003.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, March 8, 1977; UA003.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, June 14, 1977; UA003.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, September 20, 1977; UA003.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, October 18, 1977; UA003.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1977; UA003.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, January 17, 1978; UA003.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, March 15, 1978; UA003.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, April 11, 1978; UA003.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Executive Committee, Tuesday, June 20, 1978; UA003.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, September 19, 1978; UA003.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, October 17, 1978; UA003.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, November 21, 1978; UA003.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, December 19, 1978; UA003.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, January 16, 1979; UA003.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, February 20, 1979; UA003.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, March 20, 1979; UA003.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, April 17, 1979; UA003.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, May 15, 1979; UA003.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, July 17, 1979; UA003.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday September 12, 1979; UA003.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday October 3, 1979; UA003.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday November 7, 1979; UA003.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday December 5, 1979; UA003.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, January 9, 1980; UA003.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday February 6, 1980; UA003.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday March 5, 1980; UA003.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, April 2, 1980; UA003.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday May 7, 1980; UA003.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, Wednesday July 2, 1980; UA003.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, December 3, 1980; UA003.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, October 8, 1980; UA003.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, January 7, 1981; UA003.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, February 4, 1981; UA003.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, April 1, 1981; UA003.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - Executive Committee, May 6, 1981; UA003.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, July 8, 1981; UA003.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, October 7, 1981; UA003.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, November 3, 1981; UA003.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, November 17, 1981; UA003.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, December 1, 1981; UA003.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, December 15, 1981; UA003.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, 1981 -- 1982; UA003.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, February 2, 1982; UA003.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, May 18, 1982; UA003.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, July 6, 1982; UA003.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, August 3, 1982; UA003.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, September 7, 1982; UA003.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, October 5, 1982; UA003.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, March 15, 1983; UA003.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, March 23, 1983; UA003.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, May 3, 1983; UA003.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, July 12, 1983; UA003.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, August 2, 1983; UA003.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, September 20, 1983; UA003.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee, October 4, 1983; UA003.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, October 18, 1983; UA003.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, November 1, 1983; UA003.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, November 15, 1983; UA003.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, January 3, 1984; UA003.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, January 17, 1984; UA003.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, February 7, 1984; UA003.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, March 6, 1984; UA003.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, April 3, 1984; UA003.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, April 17, 1984; UA003.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, May 1, 1984; UA003.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, May 15, 1984; UA003.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, June 19, 1984; UA003.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, July 17, 1984; UA003.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, September 4, 1984; UA003.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, September 18, 1984; UA003.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, October 16, 1984; UA003.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, November 20, 1984; UA003.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, Decemeber 18, 1984; UA003.002.010.00019 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee Working Papers, January 8, 1985; UA003.002.010.00020 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, March 5, 1985; UA003.002.010.00021 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, January 22, 1985; UA003.002.010.00022 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, April 16, 1985; UA003.002.010.00023 (Box 10)
    - Executive Committee, May 7, 1985; UA003.002.011.00001 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, June 4, 1985; UA003.002.011.00002 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, July 16, 1985; UA003.002.011.00003 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, August 6, 1985; UA003.002.011.00004 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, September 3, 1985; UA003.002.011.00005 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, November 5, 1985; UA003.002.011.00006 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, December 3, 1985; UA003.002.011.00007 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, January 7, 1986; UA003.002.011.00008 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, January 21, 1986; UA003.002.011.00009 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, March 4, 1986; UA003.002.011.00010 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, March 18, 1986; UA003.002.011.00011 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, April 1, 1986; UA003.002.011.00012 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, May 6, 1986; UA003.002.011.00013 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, June 3, 1986; UA003.002.011.00014 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, June 17, 1986; UA003.002.011.00015 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, July 1, 1986; UA003.002.011.00016 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, July 28, 1986; UA003.002.011.00017 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, September 2, 1986; UA003.002.011.00018 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, September 16, 1986; UA003.002.011.00019 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, October 7, 1986; UA003.002.011.00020 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, November 4, 1986; UA003.002.011.00021 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, December 16, 1986; UA003.002.011.00022 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, January 6, 1987; UA003.002.011.00023 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, January 20, 1987; UA003.002.011.00024 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, February 17, 1987; UA003.002.011.00025 (Box 11)
    - Executive Committee, March 17, 1987; UA003.002.012.00001 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, April 1, 1987; UA003.002.012.00002 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, April 27, 1987; UA003.002.012.00003 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, May 5, 1987; UA003.002.012.00004 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, July 21, 1987; UA003.002.012.00005 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, August 4, 1987; UA003.002.012.00006 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, October 6, 1987; UA003.002.012.00007 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, September 1, 1987; UA003.002.012.00008 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, January 19, 1988; UA003.002.012.00009 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, May 3, 1988; UA003.002.012.00010 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, July 19, 1988; UA003.002.012.00011 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, September 6, 1988; UA003.002.012.00012 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, September 6, 1988; UA003.002.012.00013 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, October 18, 1988; UA003.002.012.00014 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1988; UA003.002.012.00015 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1988; UA003.002.012.00016 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, January 1989, UA003.002.012.00017 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, March 15, 1989; UA003.002.012.00018 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee, April 4, 1989; UA003.002.013.00001 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, April 4, 1989; UA003.002.013.00002 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, May 9, 1989; UA003.002.013.00003 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, June 13, 1989; UA003.002.013.00004 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, June 27, 1989; UA003.002.013.00005 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, July 11, 1989; UA003.002.013.00006 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, August 1, 1989; UA003.002.013.00007 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, September 12, 1989; UA003.002.013.00008 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, October 17, 1989; UA003.002.013.00009 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, December 12, 1989; UA003.002.013.00010 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, January 9, 1990; UA003.002.013.00011 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, June 12, 1990; UA003.002.013.00012 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, July 10, 1990; UA003.002.013.00013 (Box 13)
    - Executive Committee, August 14, 1990; UA003.002.014.00001 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, August 14, 1990; UA003.002.014.00002 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, September 4, 1990; UA003.002.014.00003 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, October 9, 1990; UA003.002.014.00004 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, November 13, 1990; UA003.002.014.00005 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, December 18, 1990; UA003.002.014.00006 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, January 8, 1991; UA003.002.014.00007 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, February 12, 1991; UA003.002.014.00008 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, April 2, 1991 (March 12), UA003.002.014.00009 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, May 14, 1991; UA003.002.014.00010 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, June 11, 1991; UA003.002.014.00011 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, June 11, 1991; UA003.002.014.00012 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, September 3, 1991; UA003.002.014.00013 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, October 1, 1991; UA003.002.014.00014 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, November 5, 1991; UA003.002.014.00015 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, December 3, 1991; UA003.002.014.00016 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, January 7, 1992; UA003.002.014.00017 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, February 4, 1992; UA003.002.015.00001 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, March 3, 1992; UA003.002.015.00002 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, April 7, 1992; UA003.002.015.00003 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, July 7, 1992; UA003.002.015.00004 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, September 1, 1992; UA003.002.015.00005 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, December 1, 1992; UA003.002.015.00006 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, October 8, 1992; UA003.002.015.00007 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee, September 1, 1992; UA003.002.094.00001 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 8, 1992; UA003.002.094.00002 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 23, 1992; UA003.002.094.00003 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 5, 1993; UA003.002.094.00004 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, February 1, 1993; UA003.002.094.00005 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, April 8, 1993; UA003.002.094.00006 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, June 1, 1993; UA003.002.094.00007 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, July 6, 1993; UA003.002.094.00008 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 7, 1993; UA003.002.094.00009 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 19, 1993; UA003.002.094.00010 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 4, 1994; UA003.002.094.00011 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, February 4, 1994; UA003.002.094.00012 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, April 5, 1994; UA003.002.094.00013 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, May 3, 1994; UA003.002.094.00014 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, June 7, 1994; UA003.002.094.00015 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, August 2, 1994; UA003.002.094.00016 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, November 1, 1994; UA003.002.094.00017 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, December 6, 1994; UA003.002.094.00018 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, January 3, 1995; UA003.002.094.00019 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, March 7, 1995; UA003.002.094.00020 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, April 4, 1995; UA003.002.094.00021 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, May 19, 1995; UA003.002.094.00022 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, September 5, 1995; UA003.002.094.00023 (Box 94)
    - Executive Committee, October 27 and 18, 1995; UA003.002.094.00024 (Box 94)